<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="vinoXML.xsl" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="vinoXML.css" ?>
<wine>
    <winedetail>
        <name>The Ned</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Pinot Noir</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>Marlborough</wineregion>
        <origin>NWZ</origin>
        <notes>A sensitively handled blend of two Pinot varieties; one where the Noir delivers a long, saturated core of
            pure berry fruit flavour with crisp acid edges and a lightly drying tannin tail whilst the Gris provides the
            perfect juxtaposition - a subtle richness that lends fruit sweetness, flesh and palate texture.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Butternut</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Syrah</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Central Coast</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>Sweet scents of watermelon, citrus and pale florals fill the air. On the palate, an array
            of strawberry and grapefruit entwine to deliver a crisp, acidic finish.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Conundrum</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Valdiguié</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Napa Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>An alluring color of rose gold, this wine offers fresh scents of watermelon, strawberries and ripe
            peaches. Floral notes come through on the nose and carry over to the palate, along with flavors of berries,
            pomegranate and citrus. Both dry and round, layers of delicate and intense fruit flavors add a degree of
            character that can be elusive in a Rosé. The finish on this wine is light and bright, with a floral quality
            blending seamlessly with the lushness of its fruit.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Domaine LaFage Miraflors</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Mourvédre</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Languedoc-Roussillon</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>Named after an old estate located in the heart of Domaine Lafage, Mas Miraflors, the Miraflors Rosé is
            sourced from old vines of Grenache Gris, nearing 80 years old, planted near the Mediterranean. Added to this
            is some Mourvedre that Jean-Marc planted here about 15 years ago. This a direct press rosé with the color
            coming from the skins of the pink Grenache Gris berries, and naturally, from the much darker Mourvedre. It
            is aged in tank for 4 months before bottling.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Gabriel Meffre Cotes du Rhone Terres de Galets</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Rhone</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>A rose of Cotes du Rhone. 60% Syrah, 40% Grenache Gris. Summer strawberries, vanilla,
            and wisps of red delicious apples. Such an amazing rose for the price. Soft, supple and very inviting! Have
            this rose with Parmesan fingerlings, apricot glazed salmon or chocolate filled croissants.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Hippolyte Reverdy Sancerre</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Pinot Noir</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Loire Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>Hippolyte Reverdy's family has been making wine in the charming village of Verdigny, a commune of
            Sancerre in the eastern Loire, for many generations. The rosé is vinified like the whites, but at slightly
            cooler temperatures.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>AIX</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Provence</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>AIX Rosé is the result of dedication and passion to make the best Provence Rosé available. When drinking
            AIX you will notice a tremendously vibrant and summery taste, the ultimate expression of the Provence. AIX
            has a bright, pale pink color and has a delicate balance of crisp acidity and soft, ripe summer fruit.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Château Gassier Esprit Gassier</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Provence</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>A very clear rosé with shades of peach; floral nose with white and yellow fruit notes (peach, apricot,
            pear); in the mouth, round and delicate with notes of white peach, mandarin and grapefruit.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Coeur Clementine</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Provence</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>Unique composition of Cinsault, Grenache, Tibouren and Mauverde. A fruity yet mineral-driven wine, light
            in color but explodes on the palate.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Mas des Bressades Cuvee Tradition</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Rhone</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>The lovely Mas des Bressades Rosé is raspberry in color. It displays delicious wild strawberry,
            raspberry, and rosé petal aromas, with a lovely underlying minerality. Powerful and pure. Fish or grilled
            meat.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
</wine>