<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="vinoXML.xsl" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="vinoXML.css" ?>
<wine>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Radio-Coteau Savoy</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Chardonnay</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>North Coast</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>The 2013 Savoy Anderson Valley Chardonnay is light straw in color. Simultaneously driven by its fruit and
            mineral character, notes of lemon rind, fresh grapefruit, and ripe pear can initially be picked out on the
            nose along with a slight flintiness. While the fruit tones remain on the palette, the mineral flintiness
            gives way to chalkiness, adding to the complexity. Additional elements of citrus blossom, white pepper and
            parsley round out the nose and palette of this wine, lending it to pair gracefully with fresh, simple
            ingredients. Drinking well in the present yet will reward a patient cellarer.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Astrolabe Marlborough</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Sauvignon Blanc</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>MarlboroughAS</wineregion>
        <origin>NWZ</origin>
        <notes>Colour/Appearance: Pale straw with green
            highlights. Aroma/Bouquet: Lemon grass, lime peel and elderflower, with background notes of white currant
            and red pepper. Palate: Medium-bodied with white peach, gooseberry and citrus flavours, and a dry mineral
            finish. Suggested Foods: Summer salads, poultry and all seafood, especially green-lipped mussels.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Saintsbury Carneros</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Chardonnay</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>Napa Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>Zesty notes of lime, kumquats and green pineapple, with heady powdered lily aromas. On the pallet this
            wine is energetic from the start with tangy citrus, white peach and cloves. Suggested Pairings: Simple
            braised chicken thighs with Meyer lemons and olives, whole grilled fish, and Cowgirl Creamery Mt. Tam or
            Cabot Clothbound Cheddar cheeses.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Grgich Hills</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Sauvignon Blanc</variety>
        <vintage>2014</vintage>
        <wineregion>Napa Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>From cool American Canyon and Carneros vineyards in the southern tip of Napa Valley. About 80% of our
            Sauvignon Blanc is planted to the Musqué clone, which provides elegant floral aromatics. We ferment 80% of
            the grapes in foudres, large French oak casks, with the remainder in previously-used small French oak
            barrels.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Seifried</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Sauvignon Blanc</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Nelson</wineregion>
        <origin>NWZ</origin>
        <notes>The 2016 Seifried Sauvignon Blanc is lively and flavoursome. Nettle, gooseberry and dried hops define the
            generous nose. Layers of varietal fruit and a zesty thread of minerally acid run the palate leaving a long,
            crisp finish.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Cape Mentelle</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Sauvignon Blanc</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Western Australia</wineregion>
        <origin>AUS</origin>
        <notes>The vibrant and aromatic blend produces a fresh, distinctive wine that accentuates the unique character
            of both varieties. Meticulous winemaking preserves the remarkable intensity of fruit flavour and provides
            the structure, weight and texture that characterise the Cape Mentelle style.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Novellum</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Chardonnay</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>Languedoc-Roussillon</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>Someone once made an unflattering comparison between Chardonnay and a part of one's anatomy best left
            unmentioned, saying, "everyone's got one, no one wants to hear about yours." Sadly Chardonnay is a victim of
            its own success and frequently a punch line despite being one of the most highly esteemed wines in its guise
            of Grand Cru Chablis or Montrachet. We are not claiming that Novellum is like these auspicious wines but we
            will argue that for its price you can hardly find better. For many years we worked with a cooperative in the
            Languedoc to make Novellum from a special site that in most years had some botrytis, giving the wine weight
            without resorting to oak. Since that time we've moved the project to the Roussillon where Jean-Marc and
            Eliane Lafage have some Chardonnay planted near the Mediterranean that makes a remarkably complex and
            mineral version of the variety. There is no botrytis here so we resort to a small percentage in barrel -
            usually less than 20%. The remainder of the wine is aged in tank on the lees of Viognier. It remains one of
            the best values in Chardonnay that you can find.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Bodega Colomé</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Torrontes</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Calchaqui Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>ARG</origin>
        <notes>Colomé Torrontés is a delicate, elegant and distinguished interpretation of this variety, with floral
            notes of roses combined with citrus aromas and a spicy hint, making it ideal to match with ethnical food,
            such as mexican, peruvian and seafood.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Trefethen</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Chardonnay</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>Napa Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>The nose opens with bursts of orange blossoms and hints of lemon cream pie. The palate is full yet
            bright, offering a pleasant viscosity and subtle notes of kiwi. The clean finish adds an exclamation point
            with elegance. Food Affinities: The perfect balance of body and acidity makes this an ideal food wine. It
            will shine with light dishes featuring shellfish, grilled fish, chicken or pasta with spring vegetables.
            Fresh tarragon as an accent herb works quite well.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Nautilus</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Sauvignon Blanc</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Marlborough</wineregion>
        <origin>NWZ</origin>
        <notes>The 2016 Nautilus Sauvignon Blanc displays intense aromas of ripe passionfruit, elderflower, limes and
            fresh herbs. The palate introduces a delightful lime/citrus based mouth-watering intensity and finishes with
            a strong textural component. Delicious upon release, this wine will improve for 3-5 years post vintage. Try
            with Snapper ceviche with chilli and lime, avocado and tomato, with coriander salsa.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
</wine>