<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="vinoXML.xsl" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="vinoXML.css" ?>
<wine>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Kenwood Jack London</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Cabernet Sauvignon</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>Sonoma County</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>
            Since our first vintage from the Jack London Ranch in 1976 it has proven itself as an outstanding producer
            of exceptional Cabernet Sauvignon. Located midway up the Eastern flanks of Sonoma Mountain it has a long
            mild growing season that creates fruit with complexity and balance. The influence of the vineyard's red
            volcanic soil and the fruity characteristics of the grapes combine to produce an outstanding, very
            distinctive Cabernet Sauvignon.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Angels Landing</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Pinot Noir</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>Sonoma County</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>
            Superior Pinot Noir from Sonoma Coast always seems to be $30 and up. Angels Landing is a steal at 16.99!
            Angels Landing has become a familiar name for great value just like Robert Mondavi, Deloach, etc. Not only
            do they make a great Napa Cabernet for the money, but also this Sonoma Coast Pinot Noir that drinks more
            like a $30 bottle of wine.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Hartford Court</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Pinot Noir</variety>
        <vintage>2014</vintage>
        <wineregion>Sonoma County</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>We love Pinot Noir and in many years make about 15 of them with fruit from the Russian River Valley,
            Sonoma Coast, Green Valley, Carneros, Anderson Valley, Marin and Oregon appellations. We feel that Pinot
            Noir makes the most seductive red wine, notable for its supple, silky texture. Pinot Noir is also known for
            expressing vineyard site characteristics in a transparent manner.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Two Hands Sexy Beast</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Cabernet Sauvignon</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>South Australia</wineregion>
        <origin>AUS</origin>
        <notes>A succulent wine with aromas of lavender, cranberries and minty floral Asian spice. This is textbook
            Cabernet Sauvignon and highlights how well McLaren Vale is situated to growing it. Color: Dark red with a
            vibrant hue. Aroma: Notes of red current, plum, bay leaf, juniper, wet clay and graphite. Palate: Round yet
            fine and detailed, this medium bodied wine is brimming with lovely fruit density. Notes of red current,
            cassis, black cherry, and plum lead the charge, supported by secondary notes of bay leaf, graphite, wet clay
            and chocolate. Starting early, tannins are savoury in nature and run long through the palate complimented by
            lovely accents of ash and coal dust. Dense and chewy through to the finish, this wine has excellent length.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Clos des Papes</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Chateauneuf-du-Pape</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>Rhone</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>For the red Chateauneuf, Clos des Papes uses up to 20% of Mourvedre in the blend. Grenache and Syrah are
            the other main components at around 50% and 10% respectively, with the balance being a mix of all the other
            permitted varieties. Clos des Papes is one of the few estates to use all permitted varieties for both red
            and white Chateauneuf. They are well-known for producing one of the most authentic and long-lived examples
            of the appellation having started estate bottling in 1896. The white Chateauneuf-du-Pape also ages extremely
            well providing great drinking pleasure for 20 years or more.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Brancaia Tre</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Sangiovese</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>Tuscany</wineregion>
        <origin>ITA</origin>
        <notes>Brancaia TRE is a wine full of character giving you drinking pleasure already at the moment of release.
            TRE stands for the three grape varieties Sangiovese, Merlot and Cabernet Sauvignon and for our three Tuscan
            estates, the basis for this wine. TRE was also our third label in 2000 so we have three good reasons to name
            it Brancaia TRE. This elegant and well structured wine, matches every cuisine. Pair with various pasta
            dishes, roasted and sautéed white meat, white poultry, fried and grilled fish.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Melville Estate</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Pinot Noir</variety>
        <vintage>2014</vintage>
        <wineregion>Central Coast</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>Brilliant ruby in color, vivid aromatics of red currants, cedar and cinnamon stick spring from the glass.
            On the palate, delicate and lifted floral notes of crushed rose petal and hibiscus are anchored by more
            tender impressions of strawberry gelatin, tangerine oil, black cherry compote and baked red apples. The
            mouthfeel is focused and vibrant, possessing a gorgeous mineral component along with lively acidity that
            augment the wine's generous and cohesive finish.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Château Puech-Haut Prestige</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>Languedoc-Roussillon</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>Château Puech-Haut has been on the critic's radar for some time - which makes sense since the property
            has employed Michel Rolland, Claude Gros and now Philippe Cambie as consulting enologist. Visionary owner
            Gérard Bru spares no expense in his quest for excellence. Located quite close to Pic Saint-Loup, in
            Saint-Drézéry, Puech-Haut is near the far western border of the Rhône valley and benefits from both its
            proximity to the mediterranean and the rugged, mountainous interior of France. There are slightly over 50
            hectares planted with Grenache, Syrah, Mourvedre, Cinsault, Carignan, Viognier, Marsanne, Roussanne,
            Grenache Blanc and Carignan Blanc. The wines from Puech-Haut are rich and lush but also show the earthy and
            mineral character of the rocky clay-limestone soils of the region.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Argiano Brunello di Montalcino</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Sangiovese Grosso</variety>
        <vintage>2011</vintage>
        <wineregion>Tuscany</wineregion>
        <origin>ITA</origin>
        <notes>Argiano's Brunello di Montalcino is distinguished by its elegance and its deep ruby red colour. It
            presents a good concentration on the mid-palate and a persistent aftertaste, with a rounded and voluptuous
            body, and interesting, silky tannins. It unites potency and elegance and looks like having a promising
            future. With its tempting perfumes of red berries and its clean freshness, the complexity of this wine
            presents an excellent balance. To fully appreciate its qualities, decant the wine at least one hour before
            serving.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Bodega Noemia de Patagonia A Lisa</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Malbec</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>Patagonia</wineregion>
        <origin>ARG</origin>
        <notes>A dense violet and plum color, with a bouquet of dark berries, cherry, minerals, and cocoa. Medium-bodied
            with an excellent structure, notes of cherry and cassis; with balanced, persistent tannins. Food Pairing: A
            flexible wine that can be served by the glass on its own; pairs well with pasta, fish, white meats and red
            meats.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
</wine>

