<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="Wine.xsl" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="vinoXML.css" ?>
<wine>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Kenwood Jack London</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Cabernet Sauvignon</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>Sonoma County</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>
            Since our first vintage from the Jack London Ranch in 1976 it has proven itself as an outstanding producer
            of exceptional Cabernet Sauvignon. Located midway up the Eastern flanks of Sonoma Mountain it has a long
            mild growing season that creates fruit with complexity and balance. The influence of the vineyard's red
            volcanic soil and the fruity characteristics of the grapes combine to produce an outstanding, very
            distinctive Cabernet Sauvignon.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Angels Landing</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Pinot Noir</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>Sonoma County</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>
            Superior Pinot Noir from Sonoma Coast always seems to be $30 and up. Angels Landing is a steal at 16.99!
            Angels Landing has become a familiar name for great value just like Robert Mondavi, Deloach, etc. Not only
            do they make a great Napa Cabernet for the money, but also this Sonoma Coast Pinot Noir that drinks more
            like a $30 bottle of wine.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Hartford Court</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Pinot Noir</variety>
        <vintage>2014</vintage>
        <wineregion>Sonoma County</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>We love Pinot Noir and in many years make about 15 of them with fruit from the Russian River Valley,
            Sonoma Coast, Green Valley, Carneros, Anderson Valley, Marin and Oregon appellations. We feel that Pinot
            Noir makes the most seductive red wine, notable for its supple, silky texture. Pinot Noir is also known for
            expressing vineyard site characteristics in a transparent manner.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Two Hands Sexy Beast</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Cabernet Sauvignon</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>South Australia</wineregion>
        <origin>AUS</origin>
        <notes>A succulent wine with aromas of lavender, cranberries and minty floral Asian spice. This is textbook
            Cabernet Sauvignon and highlights how well McLaren Vale is situated to growing it. Color: Dark red with a
            vibrant hue. Aroma: Notes of red current, plum, bay leaf, juniper, wet clay and graphite. Palate: Round yet
            fine and detailed, this medium bodied wine is brimming with lovely fruit density. Notes of red current,
            cassis, black cherry, and plum lead the charge, supported by secondary notes of bay leaf, graphite, wet clay
            and chocolate. Starting early, tannins are savoury in nature and run long through the palate complimented by
            lovely accents of ash and coal dust. Dense and chewy through to the finish, this wine has excellent length.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Clos des Papes</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Chateauneuf-du-Pape</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>Rhone</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>For the red Chateauneuf, Clos des Papes uses up to 20% of Mourvedre in the blend. Grenache and Syrah are
            the other main components at around 50% and 10% respectively, with the balance being a mix of all the other
            permitted varieties. Clos des Papes is one of the few estates to use all permitted varieties for both red
            and white Chateauneuf. They are well-known for producing one of the most authentic and long-lived examples
            of the appellation having started estate bottling in 1896. The white Chateauneuf-du-Pape also ages extremely
            well providing great drinking pleasure for 20 years or more.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Brancaia Tre</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Sangiovese</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>Tuscany</wineregion>
        <origin>ITA</origin>
        <notes>Brancaia TRE is a wine full of character giving you drinking pleasure already at the moment of release.
            TRE stands for the three grape varieties Sangiovese, Merlot and Cabernet Sauvignon and for our three Tuscan
            estates, the basis for this wine. TRE was also our third label in 2000 so we have three good reasons to name
            it Brancaia TRE. This elegant and well structured wine, matches every cuisine. Pair with various pasta
            dishes, roasted and sautéed white meat, white poultry, fried and grilled fish.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Melville Estate</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Pinot Noir</variety>
        <vintage>2014</vintage>
        <wineregion>Central Coast</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>Brilliant ruby in color, vivid aromatics of red currants, cedar and cinnamon stick spring from the glass.
            On the palate, delicate and lifted floral notes of crushed rose petal and hibiscus are anchored by more
            tender impressions of strawberry gelatin, tangerine oil, black cherry compote and baked red apples. The
            mouthfeel is focused and vibrant, possessing a gorgeous mineral component along with lively acidity that
            augment the wine's generous and cohesive finish.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Château Puech-Haut Prestige</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>Languedoc-Roussillon</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>Château Puech-Haut has been on the critic's radar for some time - which makes sense since the property
            has employed Michel Rolland, Claude Gros and now Philippe Cambie as consulting enologist. Visionary owner
            Gérard Bru spares no expense in his quest for excellence. Located quite close to Pic Saint-Loup, in
            Saint-Drézéry, Puech-Haut is near the far western border of the Rhône valley and benefits from both its
            proximity to the mediterranean and the rugged, mountainous interior of France. There are slightly over 50
            hectares planted with Grenache, Syrah, Mourvedre, Cinsault, Carignan, Viognier, Marsanne, Roussanne,
            Grenache Blanc and Carignan Blanc. The wines from Puech-Haut are rich and lush but also show the earthy and
            mineral character of the rocky clay-limestone soils of the region.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Argiano Brunello di Montalcino</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Sangiovese Grosso</variety>
        <vintage>2011</vintage>
        <wineregion>Tuscany</wineregion>
        <origin>ITA</origin>
        <notes>Argiano's Brunello di Montalcino is distinguished by its elegance and its deep ruby red colour. It
            presents a good concentration on the mid-palate and a persistent aftertaste, with a rounded and voluptuous
            body, and interesting, silky tannins. It unites potency and elegance and looks like having a promising
            future. With its tempting perfumes of red berries and its clean freshness, the complexity of this wine
            presents an excellent balance. To fully appreciate its qualities, decant the wine at least one hour before
            serving.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Bodega Noemia de Patagonia A Lisa</name>
        <category>Red Wine</category>
        <variety>Malbec</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>Patagonia</wineregion>
        <origin>ARG</origin>
        <notes>A dense violet and plum color, with a bouquet of dark berries, cherry, minerals, and cocoa. Medium-bodied
            with an excellent structure, notes of cherry and cassis; with balanced, persistent tannins. Food Pairing: A
            flexible wine that can be served by the glass on its own; pairs well with pasta, fish, white meats and red
            meats.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>The Ned</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Pinot Noir</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>Marlborough</wineregion>
        <origin>NWZ</origin>
        <notes>A sensitively handled blend of two Pinot varieties; one where the Noir delivers a long, saturated core of
            pure berry fruit flavour with crisp acid edges and a lightly drying tannin tail whilst the Gris provides the
            perfect juxtaposition - a subtle richness that lends fruit sweetness, flesh and palate texture.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Butternut</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Syrah</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Central Coast</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>Sweet scents of watermelon, citrus and pale florals fill the air. On the palate, an array
            of strawberry and grapefruit entwine to deliver a crisp, acidic finish.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Conundrum</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Valdiguié</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Napa Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>An alluring color of rose gold, this wine offers fresh scents of watermelon, strawberries and ripe
            peaches. Floral notes come through on the nose and carry over to the palate, along with flavors of berries,
            pomegranate and citrus. Both dry and round, layers of delicate and intense fruit flavors add a degree of
            character that can be elusive in a Rosé. The finish on this wine is light and bright, with a floral quality
            blending seamlessly with the lushness of its fruit.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Domaine LaFage Miraflors</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Mourvédre</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Languedoc-Roussillon</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>Named after an old estate located in the heart of Domaine Lafage, Mas Miraflors, the Miraflors Rosé is
            sourced from old vines of Grenache Gris, nearing 80 years old, planted near the Mediterranean. Added to this
            is some Mourvedre that Jean-Marc planted here about 15 years ago. This a direct press rosé with the color
            coming from the skins of the pink Grenache Gris berries, and naturally, from the much darker Mourvedre. It
            is aged in tank for 4 months before bottling.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Gabriel Meffre Cotes du Rhone Terres de Galets</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Rhone</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>A rose of Cotes du Rhone. 60% Syrah, 40% Grenache Gris. Summer strawberries, vanilla,
            and wisps of red delicious apples. Such an amazing rose for the price. Soft, supple and very inviting! Have
            this rose with Parmesan fingerlings, apricot glazed salmon or chocolate filled croissants.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Hippolyte Reverdy Sancerre</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Pinot Noir</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Loire Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>Hippolyte Reverdy's family has been making wine in the charming village of Verdigny, a commune of
            Sancerre in the eastern Loire, for many generations. The rosé is vinified like the whites, but at slightly
            cooler temperatures.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>AIX</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Provence</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>AIX Rosé is the result of dedication and passion to make the best Provence Rosé available. When drinking
            AIX you will notice a tremendously vibrant and summery taste, the ultimate expression of the Provence. AIX
            has a bright, pale pink color and has a delicate balance of crisp acidity and soft, ripe summer fruit.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Château Gassier Esprit Gassier</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Provence</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>A very clear rosé with shades of peach; floral nose with white and yellow fruit notes (peach, apricot,
            pear); in the mouth, round and delicate with notes of white peach, mandarin and grapefruit.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Coeur Clementine</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Provence</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>Unique composition of Cinsault, Grenache, Tibouren and Mauverde. A fruity yet mineral-driven wine, light
            in color but explodes on the palate.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Mas des Bressades Cuvee Tradition</name>
        <category>Rosé Wine</category>
        <variety>Grenache</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Rhone</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>The lovely Mas des Bressades Rosé is raspberry in color. It displays delicious wild strawberry,
            raspberry, and rosé petal aromas, with a lovely underlying minerality. Powerful and pure. Fish or grilled
            meat.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Radio-Coteau Savoy</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Chardonnay</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>North Coast</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>The 2013 Savoy Anderson Valley Chardonnay is light straw in color. Simultaneously driven by its fruit and
            mineral character, notes of lemon rind, fresh grapefruit, and ripe pear can initially be picked out on the
            nose along with a slight flintiness. While the fruit tones remain on the palette, the mineral flintiness
            gives way to chalkiness, adding to the complexity. Additional elements of citrus blossom, white pepper and
            parsley round out the nose and palette of this wine, lending it to pair gracefully with fresh, simple
            ingredients. Drinking well in the present yet will reward a patient cellarer.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Astrolabe Marlborough</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Sauvignon Blanc</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>MarlboroughAS</wineregion>
        <origin>NWZ</origin>
        <notes>Colour/Appearance: Pale straw with green
            highlights. Aroma/Bouquet: Lemon grass, lime peel and elderflower, with background notes of white currant
            and red pepper. Palate: Medium-bodied with white peach, gooseberry and citrus flavours, and a dry mineral
            finish. Suggested Foods: Summer salads, poultry and all seafood, especially green-lipped mussels.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Saintsbury Carneros</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Chardonnay</variety>
        <vintage>2013</vintage>
        <wineregion>Napa Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>Zesty notes of lime, kumquats and green pineapple, with heady powdered lily aromas. On the pallet this
            wine is energetic from the start with tangy citrus, white peach and cloves. Suggested Pairings: Simple
            braised chicken thighs with Meyer lemons and olives, whole grilled fish, and Cowgirl Creamery Mt. Tam or
            Cabot Clothbound Cheddar cheeses.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Grgich Hills</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Sauvignon Blanc</variety>
        <vintage>2014</vintage>
        <wineregion>Napa Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>From cool American Canyon and Carneros vineyards in the southern tip of Napa Valley. About 80% of our
            Sauvignon Blanc is planted to the Musqué clone, which provides elegant floral aromatics. We ferment 80% of
            the grapes in foudres, large French oak casks, with the remainder in previously-used small French oak
            barrels.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Seifried</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Sauvignon Blanc</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Nelson</wineregion>
        <origin>NWZ</origin>
        <notes>The 2016 Seifried Sauvignon Blanc is lively and flavoursome. Nettle, gooseberry and dried hops define the
            generous nose. Layers of varietal fruit and a zesty thread of minerally acid run the palate leaving a long,
            crisp finish.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Cape Mentelle</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Sauvignon Blanc</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Western Australia</wineregion>
        <origin>AUS</origin>
        <notes>The vibrant and aromatic blend produces a fresh, distinctive wine that accentuates the unique character
            of both varieties. Meticulous winemaking preserves the remarkable intensity of fruit flavour and provides
            the structure, weight and texture that characterise the Cape Mentelle style.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Novellum</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Chardonnay</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>Languedoc-Roussillon</wineregion>
        <origin>FRA</origin>
        <notes>Someone once made an unflattering comparison between Chardonnay and a part of one's anatomy best left
            unmentioned, saying, "everyone's got one, no one wants to hear about yours." Sadly Chardonnay is a victim of
            its own success and frequently a punch line despite being one of the most highly esteemed wines in its guise
            of Grand Cru Chablis or Montrachet. We are not claiming that Novellum is like these auspicious wines but we
            will argue that for its price you can hardly find better. For many years we worked with a cooperative in the
            Languedoc to make Novellum from a special site that in most years had some botrytis, giving the wine weight
            without resorting to oak. Since that time we've moved the project to the Roussillon where Jean-Marc and
            Eliane Lafage have some Chardonnay planted near the Mediterranean that makes a remarkably complex and
            mineral version of the variety. There is no botrytis here so we resort to a small percentage in barrel -
            usually less than 20%. The remainder of the wine is aged in tank on the lees of Viognier. It remains one of
            the best values in Chardonnay that you can find.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Bodega Colomé</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Torrontes</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Calchaqui Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>ARG</origin>
        <notes>Colomé Torrontés is a delicate, elegant and distinguished interpretation of this variety, with floral
            notes of roses combined with citrus aromas and a spicy hint, making it ideal to match with ethnical food,
            such as mexican, peruvian and seafood.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Trefethen</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Chardonnay</variety>
        <vintage>2015</vintage>
        <wineregion>Napa Valley</wineregion>
        <origin>USA</origin>
        <notes>The nose opens with bursts of orange blossoms and hints of lemon cream pie. The palate is full yet
            bright, offering a pleasant viscosity and subtle notes of kiwi. The clean finish adds an exclamation point
            with elegance. Food Affinities: The perfect balance of body and acidity makes this an ideal food wine. It
            will shine with light dishes featuring shellfish, grilled fish, chicken or pasta with spring vegetables.
            Fresh tarragon as an accent herb works quite well.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
    <winedetail>
        <name>Nautilus</name>
        <category>White Wine</category>
        <variety>Sauvignon Blanc</variety>
        <vintage>2016</vintage>
        <wineregion>Marlborough</wineregion>
        <origin>NWZ</origin>
        <notes>The 2016 Nautilus Sauvignon Blanc displays intense aromas of ripe passionfruit, elderflower, limes and
            fresh herbs. The palate introduces a delightful lime/citrus based mouth-watering intensity and finishes with
            a strong textural component. Delicious upon release, this wine will improve for 3-5 years post vintage. Try
            with Snapper ceviche with chilli and lime, avocado and tomato, with coriander salsa.
        </notes>
    </winedetail>
</wine>
