<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone = "no"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type = "text/css" href = "faq.css"?>
<!-- Paul Pearson -->
<!-- Sun, Sept 10, 2017 -->
<!-- Weird-Al-Yankovic-faq.xml -->

<FAQ>

	<title>Weird Al Yankovic FAQ</title>
	<subtitle></subtitle>
	<author>Marty "Gumby" Lick</author>
	<website>http://www.al-oholicsanonymous.com/faq/index.html</website>

	<section>
		<title>General Information</title>
		<question>
			1. What's Weird Al's latest album?
		</question>

		<answer>
			"Straight Outta Lynwood", Al's 12th studio album was released
			on
			September 26th, 2006. It includes "White and Nerdy", the parody of
			Chamillionaire's "Ridin'" as well of parodies of songs by Green Day,
			Usher, R. Kelly and Taylor Hicks! DualDisc includes PCM Stereo, 5.1
			Surround and instrumental mixes of the entire album (with on-screen
			lyrics option), plus a 9-minute behind-the-scenes documentary and 6
			BRAND NEW MUSIC VIDEOS! What more could you possibly ask for?
		</answer>

		<question>
			2. Wait, you mean Al does stuff other than just parodies?
		</question>

		<answer>
			Uh, yeah. About half of Al's catalog consists of songs he's
			written himself. If this really shocks you, then you've never
			owned a
			"Weird Al" album, you hooligan! Most fans will agree that
			his original
			songs are funnier than the parodies.
		</answer>

		<question>
			3. When will his next album come out?
		</question>

		<answer>
			Well since "Straight Outta Lynwood" just came out, it'll
			probably be
			a while.
		</answer>

		<question>
			4. What is a "style parody?"
		</question>

		<answer>
			On every album, Al has some original songs that sound almost
			like
			a parody of something else, but not quite. He replicates the
			sound
			of another band or artist. In some cases it's just a different
			genre of music, and not attributable to any single artist.
			Examples
			include "Dog Eat Dog" sounding like Talking Heads or
			"Germs" sounding
			like Nine Inch Nails.
		</answer>

		<question>
			5. Oh, I get it. So where can I find a list of what songs
			are style
			parodies and what they're supposed to sound like?
		</question>

		<answer>
			A list doesn't exist and for good reason. There's been great
			debate over the years as to what things are supposed to sound
			like.
			What one person hears as a definite Aerosmith rip someone
			else says
			"are you high? That's definitely AC/DC!" and nothing
			gets resolved. So
			you need to listen and form your own opinion,
			and then keep it to
			yourself because really, the rest of us just
			don't care. Al has
			confirmed some style parodies.
		</answer>

		<question>
			6. Was Weird Al related to "Polka King" Frankie Yankovic?

		</question>

		<answer>
			No.
		</answer>

		<question>
			7. How do you correctly pronounce and spell Al's name?

		</question>

		<answer>
			Remember that rule you learned in school that goes "I before E
			except after C"? Well, forget it. The people who came up with that
			were wrong. WRONG! When spelling "Weird", it's actually E before I
			even though there is no 'C'. Weird, huh? "W -- E -- I -- R -- D".
			Hey, speaking of the letter C, look at Al's last name, Yankovic.
			You
			see that 'C' at the end of it? Now, do you see an 'H' after
			it? No?
			GOOD! Then don't EVER pronounce his name "...vich".
			There's also no
			'K' at the end of it. You should pronounce it like
			"Yank -- Oh --
			Vick" but if you spell it with a 'K' on the end of
			it, you will be
			mocked at by all your friends, assuming you have
			friends. Even your
			imaginary friends will mock you, and that's
			sad. It's not "Jank -- ah
			-- vich" or "Crazy Al Yank -- o --
			witz". Just simply "Weird Al"
			Yankovic. If you REALLY wanna get
			anal, you're supposed to put quotes
			around "Weird Al" and not
			Yankovic. Think you can remember all that
			for next time? Try
			anyway.
		</answer>

		<question>
			8. I found some song on Napster/Morpheus/KaZaA/etc that says
			it's by
			Al. Is it really?
		</question>

		<answer>
			People tend to just assume anything funny is by "Weird Al",
			even
			if it's really bad. Other people write parodies besides Al, but
			since they're worthless nobodies, much like yourself, they don't
			get
			the credit. The only TRUE way to tell if a song is by "Weird
			Al" or
			not is to go out and buy all the CDs in Al's catalog.
			Everything else,
			is just a wasted download.
		</answer>

		<question>
			9. Does "Weird Al" have an email address?

		</question>

		<answer>
			He probably does, but you're not getting it. Drummer, Jon
			"Bermuda"
			Schwartz, maintains The Official Weird Al Page. Take a look
			at
			http://www.weirdal.com for the latest news, tons of cool
			photographs, and much, much more. You can send questions to Al
			through Ask Al on the official page. However, updates aren't regular
			and there's no guarantee he will answer your question.

			Also, if you
			want to try and get in touch with Al another way, try
			the Close
			Personal Friends of Al fan club. (See below). They now
			have an email
			address in which you can send comments and questions
			ABOUT MERCHANDISE
			ONLY. It's cpfoa@aol.com. All other inquires
			must go to the regular
			CPFOA address. Please be sure to include
			your FULL name and snail-mail
			address. In case you didn't know, Al
			does not consider song
			suggestions. Those will immediately be
			thrown out. This is for both
			personal and legal reasons. Sorry.
		</answer>

		<question>
			10. About that fan club, Close Personal Friends of Al...

		</question>

		<answer>
			CPFA used to be the official fan club for Al... and for a
			while,
			it seemed to be completely defunct. Fortunately, it is still
			alive
			today and actually serves as an office where Al can receive all
			his fan mail. Yes, he does read it all, but there are helpers who
			"weed out" all the parody song ideas people send him.
			Here's the
			address:

			Close Personal Friends of Al
			8033 Sunset Blvd.
			Los Angeles, CA
			90046

			You can email them at cpfoa@aol.com about MERCHANDISE QUESTIONS
			ONLY. All other inquires go to the address above. Be sure to
			include
			your FULL name and snail mail address. For a more detailed
			explanation, take a look at the Weird Al Information Source file
			underneath the subject Close Personal Friends of Al.
		</answer>

		<question>
			11. How can I send a parody song to Al?

		</question>

		<answer>
			Sorry, Al does not allow himself to look at other people's
			song
			ideas. Legal issues (and personal issues) prevents him from using
			suggestions from his fans or anyone else. Plus Al has a lot of his
			own song ideas already. Please don't try sending any lyrics to him
			since this is the quickest way for your letter to be recycled into
			next week's newspapers, even if there is other stuff in the letter
			as
			well.

			The best advice I can give is to record the song yourself and
			send
			it off to the Dr. Demento Show... just like what Al did when he
			was an embryo.
		</answer>

		<question>
			12. What is with his new look?

		</question>

		<answer>
			Al had LASIK eye surgery in January 1998 which corrected his
			vision. He no longer requires the uses of his glasses anymore. He
			shaved off the mustache and his hair, still naturally curly, falls
			to
			the sides, instead of up and somewhat bushy. He's had this for
			about
			five years now, and it's about time you got used to it and
			quit
			calling it 'new'.
		</answer>



		<question>
			13. Will there be a sequel to UHF?

		</question>

		<answer>
			It seems pretty unlikely nowadays. Right now Al's pretty busy
			writing songs and directing other people's videos. However, if you
			got a lot of money to throw towards Al, I'm sure he could make
			some
			time.
		</answer>

		<question>
			14. How can I get a copy of any episodes of Al-Tv or The
			Weird Al
			Show?
		</question>

		<answer>
			All 13 episodes of The Weird Al Show were released on DVD in
			August
			2006. So run out and buy as many copies as you can. You might
			be
			able to find a place that rents it too if you're cheap like that.

			Al-TV is whenever Al uses his pirate satellite to takeover the
			airwaves of MTV and aired around the release of an album. These
			gems
			however never made it to the retail market and were never
			intended to
			be released for sale. They were simply for limited
			broadcast use. The
			only way to obtain copies is to beg, plead, bribe
			or blackmail other
			fans for copy. Those fans were visionaries and
			recorded them when they
			originally aired to preserve the moments for
			all of humanity. Most
			fans work on a trading basis. That is, you
			provide them with something
			they want, and you get something you
			want in return. Good luck.
		</answer>


		<question>
			15. Will Al publish those rare songs?

		</question>

		<answer>

			If you're unfamiliar about the rare songs created by Al, I'll
			explain briefly... These are songs which Al sings in concerts only
			or
			were recorded very early in his career, and aren't available on
			any of
			his albums. The concert only stuff is called "concert only"
			for a
			reason. Either Al had a brief idea and the joke wouldn't
			survive a
			full length song, or permission was denied or never
			attempted. They're
			just some extra fun for his fans to enjoy and
			to keep 'em coming back
			for more. As for the early stuff, there's
			quite a bit out there,
			easily enough to fill an album or two, but
			don't expect to see those
			in a published collection...ever. Al has
			graciously released either a
			demo version, or previously
			unreleased song once a year to the Demento
			Society which is placed
			on their Basement Tapes CD members receive
			when they sign up for
			an annual membership.
		</answer>


		<question>
			16. Where can I find some printed lyrics?

		</question>

		<answer>
			The lyrics to all of Weird Al songs are available from the
			Dementia FAQ List Mail Auto-Responder. The quick way to get
			started is
			to send mail to jbmorris@steel.ucs.indiana.edu with the
			subject
			"LYRICS: LIST" for instructions on how to get lyrics for
			specific
			songs. For a complete list of subjects related to the Dr.
			Demento
			show, send email with the subject "LIST".
			If you have access to the
			web, you could also try these pages:
			+ Yankovic! - Published Lyrics
			http://www.yankovic.org/Category/PLyrics.html
			+ Demented Lyrics
			http://mypage.iu.edu/~jbmorris/lyrics.html#aY
		</answer>


		<question>
			17. Are there any "secret backward messages" in Al's songs?

		</question>

		<answer>
			Duh! Of course, there are "backward messages" in Al's songs.
			Ok,
			there's two The first one is in the song, "Nature Trail to Hell"
			on the album, "In-3D". The message is "Satan Eats Cheez Whiz". The
			second message is in "I Remember Larry" from the album "Bad Hair
			Day". The message is "Wow, you must have an awful lot of free time
			on
			your hands." Very funny Al. :)
		</answer>


		<question>
			18. What was "Welcome To The Fun Zone"?

		</question>

		<answer>
			[Thanks to Annie Sattler for this info]
			On June 2, 1984, NBC
			broadcast "Welcome To The Fun Zone" as a
			one-shot summer replacement
			for "Saturday Night Live." Hosted by
			Dr. Demento, it is listed in TV
			Guide as "A 'late-night party'
			blending comedy, music, and videos. It
			included: Dr. Demento,
			Howie Mandel, John Paragon, puppeteer Mark
			Weiner and the
			Weinerettes, Bozo the Clown, and John Candy in 'The
			Golf Course
			That Dripped Blood.'" Also appearing are Victoria Jackson
			and
			Weird Al (who performed "I Lost On Jeopardy" on the show).
			Al also
			wrote a theme song for the show, but it was not used. The
			song he
			wrote evolved into "Fun Zone", which is on the UHF
			Soundtrack Album.
		</answer>


		<question>
			19. I heard that some of Al's vinyl LP's had some messages
			enscribed
			in the center...
		</question>

		<answer>
			If you happen to own some of Al's music on LP format, take a
			close
			look at the inner circles on the records. Etched into most of
			Al's
			works are some surprising messages for the consumer. Could these
			be subliminal messages telling our kids to buy more Weird Al
			albums?
			Secret code being transmitted to our government? You
			decide.
			[Thanks to
			Annie Sattler for the list]
			Inscriptions at centers of vinyl LPs:

			"Weird Al" Yankovic

			Side 1: "AN ACCORDION IS A TERRIBLE THING TO
			WASTE"
			Side 2: "EAT YOUR BROCCOLI!"

			In 3-D

			Side 1: "POLKA DOWN WITH YOUR
			BAD SELF"
			Side 2: "NOW HOW MUCH WOULD YOU PAY?"

			Dare To Be Stupid

			Side
			1: MORE SONGS ABOUT TELEVISION AND FOOD
			[a takeoff on the Talking
			Heads' 1978 album title "More Songs About
			Buildings and Food]
			no
			inscription on Side 2

			Polka Party!

			Side 1: "POLKA 'TIL YOU PUKE"
			Side 2:
			WHERE'S MY LIQUID PAPER?

			Even Worse

			Side 1: "THE MAGIC RETURNS"
			Side 2:
			"100,000,000"

			No etchings were found on the LP version of the
			"Soundtrack to UHF
			(and other stuff)". And "Off The Deep End" was the
			first album NOT
			to be put into LP format. Why, you ask? Because VINYL
			IS DEAD!
			That's right! You heard me! DEAD DEAD DEAD DEAD DEAD!!!
			They're
			deader than disco! MWA HA HA HA HA!!! DEAL WITH IT! (Note: The
			opinions expressed in those last few sentences are not necessarily
			those of "Weird Al" Yankovic or anyone directly affiliated with
			him.)
		</answer>


		<question>
			20. What's the English Translation of the Spanish Lyrics in
			Taco
			Grande?
		</question>

		<answer>
			According to Cindy Caturia:
			Cheech Marin's monologue in "Taco
			Grande" (Spanish and English):

			Buenos noches Senor y bienvenidos al
			Enrico's Casa de Salsa.
			Tenemos muchos platos muy sabrosos. Se puedo
			recommendar el
			ardiente pollo al infierno. Muy delicioso. Sus ojos se
			quemaran. Su
			estomago estaran en fuego. Se quedaran en el bano por una
			semana.
			Entiendes lo que digo gringo estupido tonto?

			Good evening sir
			and welcome to Enrico's House of Salsa (or Salsa
			House). We have many
			very delicious dishes. May I recommend the
			burning chicken from hell.
			Very delicious. Your eyes will burn.
			Your stomach will be on fire.
			You'll be in the bathroom for a week!
			Do you understand what I'm
			saying you really stupid Gringo (a
			derogatory name for an American)?

			According to Allen37594@aol.com, the rest of the Spanish in the
			song
			translates to:

			I want chimichangas and chile colorado
			I have the money
			for a chopped steak
			the flautas and tamales, always really good
			and the
			stuffed pepper

			I am really hungry and now I want
			a ranch-style burrito
			No thanks, I want jalapeqos, nothing else
			Where are the nachos?
			And you
			sir, the check please.
		</answer>


		<question>
			21. What's the Yoda Chant?

		</question>

		<answer>
			If you've never attended a Weird Al concert before (yes, he
			does
			concerts) then you're missing out on quite a show!
			This was first
			introduced at the Dr.Demento 20th Anniversary Show,
			as part of Another
			One Rides The Bus. Now, Al and the band has
			been reciting this amazing
			chant in concert as part of an encore
			rendition of "Yoda" for the past
			few years, in perfect
			synchronosity, choreography, and possibly
			telepathy.
			You can find an actual written text version of the Yoda
			chant at:
			http://www.yankovic.org/WeirdAl/Unpublished/yodachant.txt
		</answer>


		<question>
			22. Did Scotti Bros. Records goof on "Permanent Record:
			Al-In-The-Box"?
		</question>

		<answer>
			In the beginning, Scotti Bros. Records had accidentally put
			the
			current "album version" of "My Bologna" instead of the "Capitol
			Records Single Version" on all of the box sets. All sets sold in
			stores now have the single version.
		</answer>


		<question>
			23. What's the difference between "The Compleat Al" and "The
			Authorized Al"?
		</question>

		<answer>
			Both came out in 1985 and both are "Mockumentaries" of Al's
			life.
			"The Compleat Al" is a video tape complete with authentic home
			movies of Al's childhood, videos, and some not-so-true stories.
			"The
			Authorized Al" is mostly the same thing in book format. Both
			are out
			of print and very difficult to find original copies of.
		</answer>


		<question>
			24. What is "Prosthetic Lips" and how can I snag a copy or
			seven?

		</question>

		<answer>
			"Prosthetic Lips" is a fans' tribute album to Al. It is a
			compilation of parodies, and remakes of Al's work as well as some
			songs simply inspired by the master. Unfortunately, all copies of
			it
			are now sold. Luckily, once again, Dave "Elvis" Rossi comes to
			the
			rescue. He gives instructions on his page at
			http://weirdal.0catch.com/pl.html on how to get your own copy.
			In
			November 2002, Insane Ian released a second tribute album
			called "Me
			Myself and I". The two projects are not related.
		</answer>


		<question>
			25. Where does Al appear in the film "The Naked Gun 2 1/2:
			The Smell
			of Fear"?
		</question>

		<answer>
			He's the thug that's holding Ed, Nordberg, and a random
			officer at
			gunpoint. His line is "You pigs....say your prayers" before
			Frank
			unknowingly knocks him out with the door.
		</answer>

		<question>
			26. Have there ever been any conventions for "Weird Al"
			fans?

		</question>

		<answer>
			Why yes, there has. Alcon was held in 1998, then Alcon 2000 in
			um,
			I forget what year, and Alcon 3 in 2002. Al showed up unannounced
			at the first one, skipped the second, and showed up as planned to
			the
			third one.
			Each one brought in a few hundred fans from around the
			country and
			the globe to participate. These were run by fans, and took
			a lot
			of work. There are no plans for another Alcon.
		</answer>

		<question>
			27. What in the world does 27 have to do with Al?

		</question>

		<answer>
			I'm glad you asked! First of all, this amazing number in Al's
			life
			was first discovered by someone on "The Midnight Star", when
			somebody asked Al if the number 27 in the "Like a Surgeon" and
			"This
			is the Life" video had some certain special meaning. Al
			hadn't
			actually noticed this number in the beginning. His final
			reply:
			"Twenty-seven is a pretty funny number".
			And thus a new age was born,
			Twenty-seven. Soon after that, the
			staff, readers, domesticated
			animals, and twenty seven kitchen
			appliances started noticing more and
			more occurances of the number
			"27". It was amazing! It was surprising!
			It was mediocre, even!
			Every where we looked, another "27" popped into
			Al's life.
			In the latest album, "Poodle Hat", there's another 27
			reference!
			In the song, "Hardware store", one line goes: "There's a
			great big
			purple sign out front saying every 27th customer will get a
			ball
			peen hammer free!"
			Now, superfan David 'Elvis' Rossi
			(dprossi@webspan.net) posts "The
			27 List" to alt.music.weird-al on the
			27th of every month. To get
			the latest version take a look at:
			+
			http://www.webspan.net/~dprossi/txt/27.list.html
		</answer>

	</section>


	<section>
		<title>Questions Relating to Specific Albums</title>
		<subtitle>"WEIRD AL" YANKOVIC (Self titled, 1983)</subtitle>
		<question>
			1. Was Buckingham Blues originally supposed to be a parody?
			Updated: 6/4/03
			According to catradohtm(catradohtm@aol.com)
		</question>

		<answer>
			Al once said that it was supposed to be a parody of "Life Goes
			on"
			(Jack and Diane), and John Cougar Meloncamp was okay with the
			idea.....but some movie studio was going to make a film version of
			the song and there would be some legal technicality involved that
			would make it hard for JCM to give Al permission, so Al decided to
			re-work the song idea as an original.
			In the 14th season of the
			Simpsons, Al and band made a cameo
			appearance in the episode "Three
			Gays of the Condo." On that
			episode, Al sang a different parody of
			"Life Goes On" simply known
			as "Homer and Marge".
			IN 3-D (1984)
		</answer>

		<question>
			2. Who did the guitar solo on "Eat It?"

		</question>

		<answer>
			Michael Jackson asked Eddie Van Halen to do the guitar solo on
			"Beat
			It", so Al asked guitar legend and producer of In-3d and his
			first
			album Rick Derringer to lay down the tracks.
		</answer>

		<subtitle>DARE TO BE STUPID (1985)</subtitle>

		<question>
			3. Did Madonna really tell Al to do "Like a Surgeon"?
		</question>

		<answer>
			This isn't 100% accurate, but it's close. Madonna had just
			released her song, "Like a Virgin" and was walking down some
			street in
			New York when she questioned out loud, "I wonder when
			'Weird Al' is
			gonna do 'Like a Surgeon'." A friend who was with
			her was also a
			friend of Al's manager and the word got back to Al.
			He thought about
			it and said "Hey, that's not bad! Mayybe I'll do
			it." This is the only
			case in which Al has created a parody based
			on a suggestion. Just to
			re-state, Al does NOT take suggestions
			for song ideas, unless you are
			Madonna, and it's a decent
			suggestion.
		</answer>

		<subtitle>POLKA PARTY (1986)</subtitle>

		<question>
			4. "Toothless People" is a parody?! Why haven't I ever heard
			the
			original?
		</question>
		<answer>
			The song is a parody of Mick Jagger's song "Ruthless People"
			which
			he wrote for the film of the same name. Al heard about the movie
			and figured, "a movie song by Mick Jagger just has to be a big
			hit."
			Al requested to get permission for the parody. The film
			flopped worse
			than a sumo wrestler on a high dive, and "Ruthless
			People" didn't even
			break the Top 40. However, shortly after the
			film was an obvious
			failure, Al was approved permission. Figuring
			it'd be an insult to
			Mick Jagger to not go ahead with the parody
			after obtaining
			permission, he recorded "Toothless People" anyway.
		</answer>

		<question>
			5. Is "Christmas At Ground Zero" banned from radio?
		</question>
		<answer> No. The FCC never said "this song can't be played." However
			there
			are many radio programming directors who feel that the song is
			just too depressing or offensive to the general population and
			have
			banned it from their stations rather than receiving a swarm
			of angry
			phone calls and letters. Obviously, those people take
			things too
			seriously. The song has been a regular on the Dr.
			Demento radio show
			each December.
		</answer>

		<subtitle>EVEN WORSE (1987)</subtitle>

		<question>
			6. Michael Jackson lent Al what?!
		</question>
		<answer>
			Michael was pleased with Al's success for "Eat It" a few
			years
			back, and when
			Al came around a second time to ask for
			permission
			to
			parody "Bad",
			Mikey agreed. He was feeling generous and
			also
			said "I'll
			even let you
			use the same subway set I just had built
			for 'Moonwalker'
			for your
			video of 'Fat'".
		</answer>

		<subtitle>UHF (1989)</subtitle>
		<question>
			7. Why does "Money For Nothin'/Beverly Hillbillies*" have
			an
			odd title, and who played guitar on it?
		</question>
		<answer>
			Well, lawyers are screwy when you take one legal work and mix
			it
			with
			another. Mark Knopfler of Dire Straits said "You can do the
			parody,
			but I have to do the guitar work." Um, OK!
		</answer>
		<subtitle>OFF THE DEEP END"(1992)</subtitle>
		<question>
			8. What's that bit at the end of the CD called?

		</question>
		<answer>
			Oh come on! It's printed on the disc and the CD cover. Duh,
			it's
			"You Don't Love Me Anymore". Man, you're lazy. I suppose the REAL
			answer you're looking for is the same as your response to the
			YDLMA
			answer: "Bite me!"
		</answer>
		<subtitle>BAD HAIR DAY (1996)</subtitle>
		<question>
			9. What's the beef with Coolio?

		</question>
		<answer>
			The story goes like this. Al wanted to do a parody of Coolio's
			'Gangstas Paradise' called "Amish Paradise". He tells his record
			label to get permission. They do. Al records and releases the
			song.
			Coolio then hears the song and says he never gave permission
			for it
			and wasn't happy about it. Al figures there was a
			communications
			breakdown somewhere and sends Coolio a public and
			sincere apology for
			the mixup saying he wouldn't have done the
			song if there was no
			permission. Coolio doesn't respond. This all
			took place back in the
			day of 1996, and by now, it's old boring
			news.
		</answer>

		<question>
			10. Why is Weezer thanked? They didn't do anything!

		</question>
		<answer>
			Well, they did something. They refused to give Al permission
			to
			include their song "Buddy Holly" in The Alternative Polka.
			Unfortunately, that came in after the liner notes had already gone
			into production, and it was assumed there wouldn't be a problem.
		</answer>

		<question>
			11. Why does my friends copy of "Bad Hair Day" have Al
			sitting, while
			mine has a red picture of his face?
		</question>
		<answer>
			There's three different versions of what's printed on the "Bad
			Hair Day" CD. The first 500,000 have Al sitting cross-legged with
			his
			hands on his head, and this is in color. After that, to try
			and save a
			few pennies, the record company printed the next batch
			in black and
			white. Then Scotti Bros. ceased to exist and the
			people at Al's new
			label made a mistake and put the "Alapalooza"
			picture on the "Bad Hair
			Day" CD. There, now go collect 'em all!
		</answer>

		<subtitle>RUNNING WITH SCISSORS (1999)</subtitle>
		<question>
			12. Is there something extra on the CD for "Running With
			Scissors"
			that's about 14 minutes long and can only be viewed on a
			computer?
		</question>
		<answer>
			Yup.
		</answer>

		<question>
			13. Am I the first person to find that?
		</question>
		<answer>
			No.

		</answer>

		<subtitle>POODLE HAT (2003)</subtitle>

		<question>
			14. Didn't Eminem refuse Al to do a parody of "Lose
			Yourself"?

		</question>
		<answer>
			Eminem gave full permission to do the parody, but asked to
			hear
			the final mix before granting permission to use his visual
			likeness in the video. Al recorded "Couch Potato" and sent it to
			Eminem's people. Figuring there wouldn't be a problem, Al started
			into pre-production of the video when the call came in from the
			Eminem camp giving a thumbs down to video permission. There was no
			reason given, but it was disappointing. It appeareared to be a
			double
			standard since Eminem himself has parodied people in his
			own videos,
			but wouldn't let someone who even had the decency to
			ask first to
			parody him. Big meanine. :(
		</answer>

		<question>
			15. In "Couch Potato", what does the line "King of Queens
			jumped the
			shark" mean?
		</question>
		<answer>
			Well, for one it means you're not up on your cultural
			references,
			but of course that's why you're reading this to being
			with. There
			is a website called, oddly enough
			htp://www.JumptheShark.com,
			which explains it's theory. In short, the
			authors felt that "Happy
			Days" was a great show. That is, until the
			episode in which Fonzie
			performs a daredevil stunt and jumps over some
			sharks while
			waterskiing.
			They believe that is the defining moment when
			the show
			started to become far-fetched and lose it's original appeal.
			And
			thus, a cultural term is born. Al is simply saying that the show
			'King of Queens' went downhill as soon as it aired.
		</answer>

		<question>
			16. What does the line "now Tivo thinks I'm gay mean" in
			"Couch
			Potato"?
		</question>
		<answer>
			Tivo is a device introduced to the US Market in 1999 and acts
			like
			a VCR recording TV shows for you, however it uses a giant hard
			drive to record them digitally. Tivo also has the feature of
			figuring
			out what kind of shows you might like to watch based on
			what you tell
			it to record. It will then automatically record it's
			findings for you
			There have been several reports or sitcom plots
			that involve Tivo
			recording shows that appear to have more and
			more 'gay' content on it
			due to the shows the users watches, or
			accidentally watches. The
			feature may be turned off on Tivo, but
			then you'll never get to
			experience the spanish version of
			Disney's "Tarzan". Your loss.
		</answer>

	</section>

</FAQ>





















